You sold your company for over a billion dollars.
So my question for you is, you know,
you made a lot of money off that.
Does money buy happiness?
No.
I think there's a certain level that money does.
I mean, I grew up very poor.
I roofed houses as a child in the Texas
heat to help my dad and then later washing dishes
with my mother.
Yes, money definitely bought happiness when
you reach a certain level beyond that.
But at a certain level,
the champagne doesn't get any better.
And at a certain level, the women don't get prettier.
At a certain level, the beaches don't get any nicer.
Just making more and more money doesn't buy happiness.
But there is probably a base level
somewhere between poverty and paying all your bills.